A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.3 FA388
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Fellowships for American Playwrights/Playwrights-in-Residence Program, 1968-1997; 272; 44 Box(es)
  - International Arts Relations, Inc. - Rivera, Jose, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 296)
  - International Arts Relations, Inc. - Rivera, Jose, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 297)
  - International Arts Relations, Inc. - Sanchez-Scott, Milcha, 1986-1987 (Box 24, Folder 298)
  - International Arts Relations, Inc. - Sanchez-Scott, Milcha, 1988-1990 (Box 24, Folder 299)
  - Intersection for the Arts, 1989-1991 (Box 24, Folder 300)
  - La Mama Experimental Theatre Club - "Angelo's Wedding" Production, 1977-1978 (Box 24, Folder 301)
  - La Mama Experimental Theatre Club - "Angelo's Wedding" Production - Evaluation, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 302)
  - La Mama Experimental Theatre Club - Baraka, Amiri, 1980-1982 (Box 24, Folder 303)
  - La Mama Experimental Theatre Club - Fierstein, Harvey, 1978-April 1979 (Box 24, Folder 304)
  - La Mama Experimental Theatre Club - Fierstein, Harvey, July 1979 (Box 24, Folder 305)
  - La Mama Experimental Theatre Club - Fierstein, Harvey, July 1979 (Box 24, Folder 306)
  - La Mama Experimental Theatre Club - Fierstein, Harvey, October 1979-1980, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 307)
  - La Mama Experimental Theatre Club - Jesurun, John, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 308)
  - La Mama Experimental Theatre Club - Jesurun, John, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 309)
  - La Mama Experimental Theatre Club - Jesurun, John, 1987-1988 (Box 24, Folder 310)
  - La Mama Experimental Theatre Club - Kennedy, Adrienne, 1973-1976 (Box 24, Folder 311)
  - L. A. Theatre Works, 1984-1985, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 312)
  - League of Theatre Artists, 1978-1980, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 313)
  - Long Wharf Theatre - Yankowitz, Susan, 1971-1974 (Box 24, Folder 314)
  - Los Angeles Actors' Theatre Foundation, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 315)
  - Los Angeles Actors' Theatre Foundation, 1980-1982 (Box 25, Folder 316)
  - Los Angeles Actors' Theatre Foundation, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 317)
  - Los Angeles Actors' Theatre Foundation, 1987, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 318)
  - Los Angeles Actors' Theatre Foundation - Holden, Joan, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 319)
  - Los Angeles Actors' Theatre Foundation - Holden, Joan, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 320)
  - Los Angeles Actors' Theatre Foundation - Holden, Joan, 1985, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 321)
  - Mabou Mines Development Foundation, Inc. - Breuer, Lee, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 322)
  - Mabou Mines Development Foundation, Inc. - Breuer, Lee, 1986-1989 (Box 25, Folder 323)
  - Mabou Mines Development Foundation, Inc. - Overmyer, Eric, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 324)
  - Mabou Mines Development Foundation, Inc. - Overmyer, Eric, 1987-1990 (Box 25, Folder 325)
  - Magic Theatre Foundation, Omaha - Grant Actions, 1973-1983 (Box 25, Folder 326)
  - Magic Theatre Foundation, Omaha, 1972-1974 (Box 26, Folder 327)
    See also Box 44, Folder 10.
  - Magic Theatre Foundation, Omaha, 1975-1976 (Box 26, Folder 328)
  - Magic Theatre Foundation, Omaha, 1977-1979 (Box 26, Folder 329)
  - Magic Theatre Foundation, Omaha, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 330)
  - Magic Theatre Foundation, Omaha, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 331)
  - Magic Theatre Foundation, Omaha, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 332)
  - Magic Theatre Foundation, Omaha, 1983-1986 (Box 26, Folder 333)
  - Magic Theatre Foundation, Omaha - Terry, Megan, 1973-1976 (Box 26, Folder 334)
  - Magic Theatre Foundation, Omaha - Terry, Megan, June 1986 (Box 26, Folder 335)
  - Magic Theatre Foundation, Omaha - Terry, Megan, July 1986-1990 (Box 26, Folder 336)
  - Magic Theatre, Inc., Berkeley, 1972-1973 (Box 26, Folder 337)
  - Magic Theatre, Inc., Berkeley, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 338)
  - Magic Theatre, Inc., Berkeley, 1975-1976 (Box 26, Folder 339)
  - Magic Theatre, Inc., Berkeley, 1977-1979 (Box 27, Folder 340)
  - Magic Theatre, Inc., Berkeley, 1980-1982 (Box 27, Folder 341)
  - Magic Theatre, Inc., Berkeley - Evaluation, 1974-1976, 1980, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 342)
  - Magic Theatre, Inc., Berkeley - Supplementary Material (I), October 1976; Folder 1 of 3 (Box 27, Folder 343)
  - Magic Theatre, Inc., Berkeley - Supplementary Material (II), October 1976; Folder 2 of 3 (Box 27, Folder 344)
  - Magic Theatre, Inc., Berkeley - Supplementary Material (III), October 1976; Folder 3 of 3 (Box 27, Folder 345)
  - Magic Theatre, Inc., Berkeley - Bullins, Ed, 1983-1984 (Box 27, Folder 346)
  - Magic Theatre, Inc., Berkeley - Bullins, Ed - Supplementary Material (I), 1983; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 27, Folder 347)
  - Magic Theatre, Inc., Berkeley - Bullins, Ed - Supplementary Material (II), 1983; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 27, Folder 348)
  - Magic Theatre, Inc., Berkeley - Shank, Adele Edling, 1980-1981 (Box 27, Folder 349)
  - Magic Theatre, Inc., Berkeley - Shank, Adele Edling, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 350)
  - Magic Theatre, Inc., Berkeley - Shepard, Sam (I), 1975-1976 (Box 27, Folder 351)
  - Magic Theatre, Inc., Berkeley - Shepard, Sam (II), 1974-1976 (Box 27, Folder 352)
  - Magic Theatre, Inc., Berkeley - Wanshel, Jeffrey, 1969-1972 (Box 27, Folder 353)
  - Magic Theatre, Inc., Berkeley - Wanshel, Jeffrey, 1973, 1976-1977 (Box 28, Folder 354)
  - Manhattan Project, 1972-1974 (Box 28, Folder 355)
  - Manhattan Project, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 356)
  - Manhattan Theatre Club, Inc. - Gurney, A. R., Jr., 1976-1977, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 357)
  - Manhattan Theatre Club, Inc. - Gurney, A. R., Jr. - Evaluation, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 358)
  - Manhattan Theatre Club, Inc. - McNally, Terrence, [1985] (Box 28, Folder 359)
  - Manhattan Theatre Club, Inc. - McNally, Terrence, [1985] (Box 28, Folder 360)
  - Manhattan Theatre Club, Inc. - McNally, Terrence, 1985-1986, 1988-1989 (Box 28, Folder 361)
  - Manhattan Theatre Club, Inc. - Sherman, Martin, 1984-1986 (Box 28, Folder 362)
  - MET Theatre - Steppling, John, 1983-1985 (Box 28, Folder 363)
  - Milwaukee Repertory Theater - Gray, Amlin, 1980-1981 (Box 28, Folder 364)
  - Milwaukee Repertory Theater - Gray, Amlin, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 365)
  - Missouri Repertory Theatre, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 366)
  - Missouri Repertory Theatre, 1981-1982 (Box 29, Folder 367)
  - Muhlenberg College - Weiss, Jeff, 1980-1982 (Box 29, Folder 368)
  - Negro Ensemble Company - Carter, Steve, 1979-1982 (Box 29, Folder 369)
  - Negro Ensemble Company - Edwards, Gus, 1978-1979, 1981-1982 (Box 29, Folder 370)
  - Negro Ensemble Company - Evans-Charles, Martie, 1972-1979 (Box 29, Folder 371)
  - Negro Ensemble Company - Fuller, Charles, 1975-1977 (Box 29, Folder 372)
  - Negro Ensemble Company - Fuller, Charles - Evaluation, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 373)
  - Negro Ensemble Company - Harrison, Paul Carter, September 1985 (Box 29, Folder 374)
  - Negro Ensemble Company - Harrison, Paul Carter, September 1985 (Box 29, Folder 375)
  - Negro Ensemble Company - Harrison, Paul Carter, December 1985-1986, 1988-1989 (Box 29, Folder 376)
  - New Federal Theatre - Rahman, Aishah, 1988-1989, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 377)
  - New Playwrights' Theatre, 1978-July 1979 (Box 29, Folder 378)
  - New Playwrights' Theatre, September 1979-1982 (Box 29, Folder 379)
  - New Playwrights' Theatre - Tavel, Ronald, 1977-1979 (Box 29, Folder 380)
  - New Playwrights' Theatre - Tavel, Ronald - Evaluation, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 381)
  - New York Shakespeare Festival - Babe, Thomas, 1976-1979, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 382)
  - New York Shakespeare Festival - Babe, Thomas - Evaluation, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 383)
  - New York Shakespeare Festival - Breuer, Lee, 1980-1981 (Box 30, Folder 384)
  - New York Shakespeare Festival - Guare, John, 1976-1977 (Box 30, Folder 385)
  - New York Shakespeare Festival - Guare, John, 1978-1979, 1981-1982 (Box 30, Folder 386)
  - New York Shakespeare Festival - Guare, John - Evaluation, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 387)
  - New York Shakespeare Festival - Hwang, David, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 388)
  - New York Shakespeare Festival - Hwang, David, 1983-1985 (Box 30, Folder 389)
  - New York Shakespeare Festival - Hwang, David - Supplementary Material (I), 1982; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 30, Folder 390)
  - New York Shakespeare Festival - Hwang, David - Supplementary Material (II), 1982; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 30, Folder 391)
  - New York Shakespeare Festival - Innaurato, Albert, 1976-1979, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 392)
  - New York Shakespeare Festival - Innaurato, Albert - Evaluation, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 393)
  - New York Shakespeare Festival - Lamb, Myrna, 1971-1973, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 394)
  - New York Shakespeare Festival - McAnuff, Des, 1979-October 1980 (Box 30, Folder 395)
  - New York Shakespeare Festival - McAnuff, Des, October 1980 (Box 30, Folder 396)
  - New York Shakespeare Festival - McAnuff, Des, October 1980 (Box 30, Folder 397)
  - New York Shakespeare Festival - McAnuff, Des, 1981-1982 (Box 31, Folder 398)
  - New York Shakespeare Festival - Noonan, John Ford, 1972-1973, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 399)
  - New York Shakespeare Festival - Pinero, Miguel, 1977-1979, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 400)
  - New York Shakespeare Festival - Pinero, Miguel - Evaluation, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 401)
  - New York Shakespeare Festival - Rabe, David, July 1980 (Box 31, Folder 402)
  - New York Shakespeare Festival - Rabe, David, July 1980 (Box 31, Folder 403)
  - New York Shakespeare Festival - Rabe, David, July-August 1980 (Box 31, Folder 404)
  - New York Shakespeare Festival - Rabe, David, 1981-1983 (Box 31, Folder 405)
  - New York Shakespeare Festival - Ribman, Ronald (I), 1974-1975, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 406)
  - New York Shakespeare Festival - Ribman, Ronald (II), 1974-1976, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 407)
  - New York Shakespeare Festival - White, Edgar, 1973-1975 (Box 31, Folder 408)
  - New York Shakespeare Festival - White, Edgar, 1984-February 1987 (Box 31, Folder 409)
  - New York Shakespeare Festival - White, Edgar, February 1987-1988 (Box 31, Folder 410)
  - New York Theater Strategy - Bernard, Kenneth (I), 1975 (Box 31, Folder 411)
  - New York Theater Strategy - Bernard, Kenneth (II), 1974-1975 (Box 31, Folder 412)
  - New York Theater Strategy - Bernard, Kenneth (II), 1976 (Box 31, Folder 413)
  - New York Theater Strategy - Bernard, Kenneth (II), 1977, 1980-1981, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 414)
  - New York Theater Strategy - Starkweather, David, 1977-1978, 1980-1982 (Box 31, Folder 415)
  - New York Theater Strategy - Starkweather, David - Evaluation, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 416)
  - Nightfire Theater, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 417)
  - Nightfire Theater, 1984-1985 (Box 32, Folder 418)
    See also Box 44, Folder 11.
  - Odyssey Theatre Ensemble (I), 1975, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 419)
  - Odyssey Theatre Ensemble (II), 1974-1977, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 420)
  - Ontological-Hysteric Theater, Inc. - Forman, Richard (I), 1973-1975 (Box 32, Folder 421)
  - Ontological-Hysteric Theater, Inc. - Forman, Richard (II), 1973-1975 (Box 32, Folder 422)
    See also Box 44, Folder 12.
  - Open Theatre - Van Itallie, Jean-Claude, 1972-1976 (Box 32, Folder 423)
  - Organic Theater (I), 1973-1975, 1977-1978, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 424)
  - Organic Theater (II), 1972-1974 (Box 32, Folder 425)
  - Organic Theater (II), 1975-1977 (Box 32, Folder 426)
  - Organic Theater (II), 1978 (Box 32, Folder 427)
  - Organic Theater (II), 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 428)
  - Organic Theater - Evaluation, 1974-1983 (Box 32, Folder 429)
  - Organic Theater - Supplementary Material (I), 1976; Folder 1 of 4 (Box 33, Folder 430)
  - Organic Theater - Supplementary Material (II), 1976; Folder 2 of 4 (Box 33, Folder 431)
  - Organic Theater - Supplementary Material (III), 1976; Folder 3 of 4 (Box 33, Folder 432)
  - Organic Theater - Supplementary Material (III), 1976; Folder 4 of 4 (Box 33, Folder 433)
  - Padua Hills Playwrights' Workshop/Festival - Epstein, Martin, 1982-September 1984 (Box 33, Folder 434)
  - Padua Hills Playwrights' Workshop/Festival - Epstein, Martin, September 1984-1986, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 435)
  - Pan Asian Repertory Theatre, Inc., 1985 (Box 33, Folder 436)
  - Pan Asian Repertory Theatre, Inc., 1986 (Box 33, Folder 437)
  - Pan Asian Repertory Theatre, Inc., 1987 (Box 33, Folder 438)
  - Pan Asian Repertory Theatre, Inc., 1988 (Box 33, Folder 439)
  - Performance Group - LeCompte, Elizabeth, and Gray, Spalding, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 440)
  - Performance Group - LeCompte, Elizabeth, and Gray, Spalding, 1980-1982 (Box 34, Folder 441)
  - Perseverance Theatre, February 1984 (Box 34, Folder 442)
  - Perseverance Theatre, March 1984-1985 (Box 34, Folder 443)
  - Perseverance Theatre, 1986-1989 (Box 34, Folder 444)
  - Perseverance Theatre, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 445)
  - Philadelphia Festival Theatre for New Plays, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 446)
  - Philadelphia Festival Theatre for New Plays, 1986 (Box 34, Folder 447)
  - Philadelphia Festival Theatre for New Plays, 1987-1989 (Box 34, Folder 448)
  - Pipeline, Inc., 1986-1989 (Box 34, Folder 449)
  - Playhouse in the Park - Fornes, Maria Irene, 1971-1973 (Box 35, Folder 450)
  - Playwrights Horizons - Bell, Neal, July 1985 (Box 35, Folder 451)
  - Playwrights Horizons - Bell, Neal, July 1985 (Box 35, Folder 452)
  - Playwrights Horizons - Bell, Neal, September 1985-1988 (Box 35, Folder 453)
  - Playwrights Horizons - Lucas, Craig, August 1987 (Box 35, Folder 454)
  - Playwrights Horizons - Lucas, Craig, August 1987-1988 (Box 35, Folder 455)
  - Playwrights Horizons - Lucas, Craig, 1989-1993, 1997 (Box 35, Folder 456)
    Time sensitive material - Open in 2018.
  - Playwrights Horizons - Whyte, Ron, 1979-April 1980 (Box 35, Folder 457)
  - Playwrights Horizons - Whyte, Ron, May 1980-1983 (Box 35, Folder 458)
  - Playwrights Horizons - Whyte, Ron - Supplementary Material (I), 1979; Folder 1 of 8 (Box 35, Folder 459)
  - Playwrights Horizons - Whyte, Ron - Supplementary Material (II), 1979; Folder 2 of 8 (Box 35, Folder 460)
  - Playwrights Horizons - Whyte, Ron - Supplementary Material (III), 1979; Folder 3 of 8 (Box 35, Folder 461)
  - Playwrights Horizons - Whyte, Ron - Supplementary Material (IV), 1979; Folder 4 of 8 (Box 35, Folder 462)
  - Playwrights Horizons - Whyte, Ron - Supplementary Material (V), 1979; Folder 5 of 8 (Box 36, Folder 463)
  - Playwrights Horizons - Whyte, Ron - Supplementary Material (VI), [1980]; Folder 6 of 8 (Box 36, Folder 464)
  - Playwrights Horizons - Whyte, Ron - Supplementary Material (VII), [1980]; Folder 7 of 8 (Box 36, Folder 465)
  - Playwrights Horizons - Whyte, Ron - Supplementary Material (VIII), 1979-1980; Folder 8 of 8 (Box 36, Folder 466)
  - Playwrights Unlimited, Inc., 1988-1989 (Box 36, Folder 467)
  - Portland Stage Company, July 1985 (Box 36, Folder 468)
  - Portland Stage Company, July 1985 (Box 36, Folder 469)
  - Portland Stage Company, 1986-1988 (Box 36, Folder 470)
  - Princeton University Theatre Company - Commire, Anne, 1978-1979 (Box 36, Folder 471)
  - Provisional Theatre Foundation (I), 1973-1974, 1979-1980 (Box 36, Folder 472)
  - Provisional Theatre Foundation (II), 1972-1973 (Box 36, Folder 473)
  - Provisional Theatre Foundation (II), 1974-1975, 1978-1980 (Box 36, Folder 474)
  - Provisional Theatre Foundation - Yankowitz, Susan (I), 1974-1975 (Box 36, Folder 475)
  - Provisional Theatre Foundation - Yankowitz, Susan (II), 1974-1977 (Box 36, Folder 476)
  - Puerto Rican Traveling Theatre Company, Inc., July 1987 (Box 36, Folder 477)
  - Puerto Rican Traveling Theatre Company, Inc., July 1987 (Box 37, Folder 478)
  - Puerto Rican Traveling Theatre Company, Inc., July 1987 (Box 37, Folder 479)
  - Puerto Rican Traveling Theatre Company, Inc., 1988-1991, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 480)
  - Ridiculous Theatrical Company - Ludlam, Charles, 1975-1980, 1982 (Box 37, Folder 481)
  - Ridiculous Theatrical Company - Ludlam, Charles - Evaluation, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 482)
  - River Arts Repertory - Jenkin, Len - Grant Action, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 483)
  - River Arts Repertory - Jenkin, Len, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 484)
  - River Arts Repertory - Jenkin, Len, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 485)
  - River Arts Repertory - Jenkin, Len, 1986-1988 (Box 37, Folder 486)
  - River Arts Repertory - Nelson, Richard, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 487)
  - River Arts Repertory - Nelson, Richard, 1988-1992 (Box 37, Folder 488)
  - Roadside Attractions, Inc., 1987-1990 (Box 37, Folder 489)
  - Roadside Attractions, Inc., 1986-1989 (Box 37, Folder 490)
  - St. Nicholas Theater Company, 1979-1980 (Box 38, Folder 491)
  - St. Nicholas Theater Company, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 492)
  - St. Nicholas Theater Company - Mamet, David, 1976 (Box 38, Folder 493)
  - St. Nicholas Theater Company - Mamet, David, 1977-January 1978 (Box 38, Folder 494)
  - St. Nicholas Theater Company - Mamet, David, February 1978-1979 (Box 38, Folder 495)
  - St. Nicholas Theater Company - Mamet, David - Evaluation, 1980 (Box 38, Folder 496)
  - Seattle Repertory Theatre, 1976-1977 (Box 38, Folder 497)
  - Seattle Repertory Theatre, 1978-May 1981 (Box 38, Folder 498)
  - Seattle Repertory Theatre, June 1981-1982 (Box 38, Folder 499)
  - Second Stage Theatre - Baitz, Jon Robin, August 1988 (Box 38, Folder 500)
  - Second Stage Theatre - Baitz, Jon Robin, August 1988-1991 (Box 38, Folder 501)
  - Second Stage Theatre - Howe, Tina, April-June 1983 (Box 38, Folder 502)
  - Second Stage Theatre - Howe, Tina, July 1983-1984 (Box 38, Folder 503)
  - Second Stage Theatre - Howe, Tina - Supplementary Material (I), 1983; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 39, Folder 504)
  - Second Stage Theatre - Howe, Tina - Supplementary Material (II), 1983; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 39, Folder 505)
  - Seven Stages, Inc., 1988-1989, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 506)
  - Silvera Writers' Workshop Foundation, 1978-1979 (Box 39, Folder 507)
  - Silvera Writers' Workshop Foundation, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 508)
  - Silvera Writers' Workshop Foundation, 1981-1982 (Box 39, Folder 509)
  - Silvera Writers' Workshop Foundation, 1983-1985 (Box 39, Folder 510)
  - Soho Repertory Theatre, Inc. - Wellman, Mac - Grant Action, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 511)
  - Soho Repertory Theatre, Inc. - Wellman, Mac, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 512)
  - Soho Repertory Theatre, Inc. - Wellman, Mac, 1988-1989, 1991, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 513)
  - South Coast Repertory, Inc., 1985 (Box 39, Folder 514)
  - South Coast Repertory, Inc., 1986-1988 (Box 39, Folder 515)
  - Stages, Inc., 1988 (Box 39, Folder 516)
  - Stages, Inc., 1989 (Box 40, Folder 517)
  - Stages, Inc., 1989, 1991 (Box 40, Folder 518)
  - Steppenwolf Theatre Company, 1984-1987, 1989 (Box 40, Folder 519)
  - Theater for the New City Foundation, Inc. - Drexler, Rosalyn, 1985-1986, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 520)
  - Theater for the New City Foundation, Inc. - Fornes, Maria Irene, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 521)
  - Theater for the New City Foundation, Inc. - Fornes, Maria Irene, 1985, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 522)
  - Theater for the New City Foundation, Inc. - Kondoleon, Harry, 1988-1989 (Box 40, Folder 523)
  - Theater for the New City Foundation, Inc. - Machado, Eduardo, August 1984 (Box 40, Folder 524)
  - Theater for the New City Foundation, Inc. - Machado, Eduardo, August 1984 (Box 40, Folder 525)
  - Theater for the New City Foundation, Inc. - Machado, Eduardo, August 1984 (Box 40, Folder 526)
  - Theater for the New City Foundation, Inc. - Machado, Eduardo, November 1984-1985, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 527)
  - Theatre and Arts Foundation of San Diego County - Wanshel, Jeff, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 528)
  - Theatre and Arts Foundation of San Diego County - Wanshel, Jeff, 1988-1991, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 529)
  - Theatre for a New Audience, Inc. - Cloud, Darrah, 1988 (Box 41, Folder 530)
  - Theatre for a New Audience, Inc. - Cloud, Darrah, 1988-1991 (Box 41, Folder 531)
  - Theatre, Inc. - Franklin, J. e., 1979 (Box 41, Folder 532)
  - Theatre, Inc. - Franklin, J. e., 1980 (Box 41, Folder 533)
  - Theatre, Inc. - Franklin, J. e., February-April 1981 (Box 41, Folder 534)
  - Theatre, Inc. - Franklin, J. e., April-July 1981 (Box 41, Folder 535)
  - Theatre-in-the-Red, 1984-1985, 1987-1988 (Box 41, Folder 536)
  - Theatre Three, Inc., 1983-1984 (Box 41, Folder 537)
  - Theatre X, 1979-1980 (Box 41, Folder 538)
  - Theatre X, 1981-1982, 1984 (Box 41, Folder 539)
  - Trinity Square Repertory Company (I), 1975, 1981 (Box 41, Folder 540)
  - Trinity Square Repertory Company (II), 1975-1978, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 541)
  - Trinity Square Repertory Company - Evaluation, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 542)
  - Victory Gardens Theater, 1985 (Box 42, Folder 543)
  - Victory Gardens Theater, 1986 (Box 42, Folder 544)
  - Victory Gardens Theater, 1987-1990 (Box 42, Folder 545)
  - Victory Gardens Theater - Supplementary Material, 1985-1987 (Box 42, Folder 546)
  - Vineyard Theatre & Workshop Center, Inc. - Shanley, John Patrick, July 1986 (Box 42, Folder 547)
  - Vineyard Theatre & Workshop Center, Inc. - Shanley, John Patrick, July-December 1986 (Box 42, Folder 548)
  - Vineyard Theatre & Workshop Center, Inc. - Shanley, John Patrick, 1987-1989 (Box 42, Folder 549)
  - Virginia Stage Company - Havis, Allan, 1986-1992 (Box 42, Folder 550)
  - Whole Theatre Company - Linney, Romulus - Grant Action, 1986 (Box 42, Folder 551)
  - Whole Theatre Company - Linney, Romulus, July 1985 (Box 42, Folder 552)
  - Whole Theatre Company - Linney, Romulus, July 1985 (Box 42, Folder 553)
  - Whole Theatre Company - Linney, Romulus, December 1985-1988 (Box 43, Folder 554)
  - Wisdom Bridge Theatre, 1981-1982 (Box 43, Folder 555)
  - Wisdom Bridge Theatre, 1983 (Box 43, Folder 556)
  - Wooster Group, Inc. - Gray, Spalding, 1986-1987, 1989 (Box 43, Folder 557)
  - Yale University - Commire, Anne, 1979-1981 (Box 43, Folder 558)
  - Yale University - Glass, Joanna McClelland, September 1984 (Box 43, Folder 559)
  - Yale University - Glass, Joanna McClelland, September 1984 (Box 43, Folder 560)
  - Yale University - Glass, Joanna McClelland, September-December 1984 (Box 43, Folder 561)
  - Yale University - Glass, Joanna McClelland, 1985-1988 (Box 43, Folder 562)
    See also Box 44, Folder 13.
  - Yale University - Jacker, Corinne, 1978-1980 (Box 43, Folder 563)
  - Yale University - Kopit, Arthur, 1978-1979 (Box 43, Folder 564)
  - Yale University - Kopit, Arthur - Evaluation, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 565)
  - Yale University - Wilson, August, 1982-1983 (Box 43, Folder 566)
  - Yale University - Wilson, August, 1984-1986 (Box 43, Folder 567)
  - Yale University - Wilson, Lanford, 1972-1974 (Box 43, Folder 568)
  - Oversized Material from Boxes 2-8, Folders 15 and 81-83 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    1982 Actors Theatre of Louisville (1980-1983)
  - Oversized Material from Box 9, Folder 99: American Place Theatre (1982-1983) (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Oversized Material from Box 10, Folder 123: American Place Theatre - Weiss, Jeff (December 1979-1981) (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Oversized Material from Box 11, Folders 133 and 136 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    Asian American Theater Workshop (1981-1985) Available Potential Enterprises, Ltd. (1988-1989)
  - Oversized Material from Box 12, Folder 140: Berkeley Stage Company (1981-1983) (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Oversized Material from Box 12, Folder 147: Broom Street Theater (1977-1980) (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Oversized Material from Boxes 12-13, Folders 148 and 157 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    Broom Street Theater (1983-1984) Center State Associates, Inc. (1986-1989)
  - Oversized Material from Boxes 18-21, Folders 217-264 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    Dashiki Project Theatre (1984-1985, 1987) Empty Space Association (1984) Free Southern Theater, Inc. (II) (1975-1977)
  - Oversized Material from Boxes 22-24, Folders 283-298 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    Illusion Theater and School, Inc. (1985, 1987) International Arts Relations, Inc. (1979-1980, March 1983, 1984-1986) International Arts Relations, Inc. - Lima, Rafael (1989-1990) International Arts Relations, Inc. - Sanchez-Scott, Milcha (1986-1987)
  - Oversized Material from Box 26, Folders 327-329: Magic Theatre Foundation, Omaha (1972-1979) (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Oversized Material from Box 32, Folder 418: Nightfire Theater (1984-1985) (Box 44, Folder 11)